ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Southern California Joint Board and California Garment Manufacturing Co. (Work Wear Corp., Inc.), 1978-1987 (Box 118, Folder 32)
- Southern Organizational Department and Cam Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 118, Folder 33)
- Rochester Joint Board and Cap-Roc, Inc., 1968 (Box 118, Folder 34)
- General Office and Carbon Hill Manufacturing Corp., 1960 (Box 118, Folder 35)
- Tannery and Leather Workers' Union Local #1712 and Care Leather Finishing, Inc., 1970-1974 (Box 118, Folder 36)
- Minnesota Joint Board and H.W. Carter & Sons, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 37)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Carteret Products Co., 1975 (Box 118, Folder 38)
- Toronto Joint Board and Caulfeild, Burns and Gibson, Ltd., 1987 (Box 118, Folder 39)
- General Office and Central Apparel Corp., 1956-1970 (Box 118, Folder 40)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Central Pennsylvania Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 118, Folder 41)
- Boston Joint Board and Central Sportswear Manufacturing Co., 1954-1966 (Box 118, Folder 42)
- California Joint Board, Local #1414G and Century Data, Inc., 1987 (Box 118, Folder 43)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union, Local #145 and Century Glove Corp., 1965-1978 (Box 118, Folder 44)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Century Industries, Inc., 1973-1979 (Box 118, Folder 45)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Charmoll, Inc., 1961-1970 (Box 118, Folder 46)
- Los Angeles Joint Board and Charms Custom Pants, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 47)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Cherry & Co., 1958-1972 (Box 118, Folder 48)
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board and Chester Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1967-1976 (Box 118, Folder 49)
- Chicago Joint Board and Chicago Neckwear Co., 1973 (Box 118, Folder 50)
- New York Joint Board and Chordas Leather, Inc., 1981 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Southern Organizational Department and Cinderella Knitting Mills, 1975-1978 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- California Joint Board and Cintas, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Cisco Casuals, Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Clair Glove Co., 1966-1976 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  Local #1714 and Local #292
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union Local #1712 and Clark Leather Splitting Co., Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Classic Custom Tailors, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Cleveland Coat Front Co., 1963-1971 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Clover Cravat Co., 1958-1973 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Coane Knitting Mills, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Cohen Bros. Specialties, Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 119, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Colony Cleaners, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Commercial St. Edmunds Laundry Corp., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Cook United, Inc., 1975-1981 (Box 119, Folder 14)
- Baltimore Joint Board and Corman & Wasserman, Inc. (The Loudon Manufacturing Co.), 1957-1972 (Box 119, Folder 15)
- Northern California Joint Board and Cornell of California, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Corona Laundry Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Cortshire Clothes Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 119, Folder 18)
- Southern California Joint Board and Court Casuals, 1978-1981 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  Outdoor Sports Industries, Brown Group, Inc.
- New York Joint Board and Crane Mayos Clothes, Inc., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 20)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Crescendoe Gloves, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 21)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Crescent Wall Systems, Inc. and Crescent Coating, Inc., 1985 (Box 119, Folder 22)
- General Office and Curtis Manufacturing Co, Inc., 1967 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  Orlando, FL
- Southern Organizational Department and Damon of Alabama, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 119, Folder 24)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Dan-Deb Manufacturing, Inc., 1978 (Box 119, Folder 25)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Dance Togs, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 119, Folder 26)
- Southern Organizational Department and Day's, Inc. (Decherd-Franklin Co, Inc.), 1965-1977 (Box 119, Folder 27)
- Massachusetts, Local #377 and Deerfield Manufacturing Co., 1957-1965 (Box 119, Folder 28)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Alfred Del Buono, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 29)
- New York Joint Board and Dell Clothing Co, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 119, Folder 30)
- General Office and Delta Manufacturing Corp., 1968 (Box 119, Folder 31)
- New England Joint Board, Local #377 and #559 and Delton Shirtmakers, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 119, Folder 32)
- Chicago Joint Board and Devon Leather Sportswear, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 33)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and A. Di Nella & Sons, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 34)
- New York Joint Board and Dorson Clothes Co., 1977-1980 (Box 119, Folder 35)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Dubin Adams Laundry, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 36)
- Chicago Joint Board and J.A. Dubow Sporting Goods Co. (Golf Ball, Inc.), 1969-1972 (Box 119, Folder 37)
- Amalgamated Services and Allied Industries and Dyckman Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 38)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and E & A Tailoring Co., 1982 (Box 119, Folder 39)
- General Office and E & W of Illmo, Inc., 1961-1975 (Box 119, Folder 40)
  Missouri
- New York Joint Board and Eagle Clothes, Inc., 1981 (Box 119, Folder 41)
- New York Joint Board and Eagle Pants Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 42)
- General Office and Elba Apparel, Inc., 1966 (Box 119, Folder 43)
  Alabama
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Elite Laundry, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 44)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Elite Linen Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 45)
- New Jersey, Local #126 and Elizabeth Shirt co., 1958 (Box 119, Folder 46)
- General Office and Enterprise Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 119, Folder 47)
- New York Joint Board and Enzel-Arthur Richards Manufacturing, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 48)
- Northern California Joint Board and Ernst, Inc., 1962-1972 (Box 119, Folder 49)
- New York Joint Board and Eton Hall Clothes, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 50)
- General Office and Eutaw Apparel Corp., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 51)
- General Office and Evergreen Textiles, Inc., 1966 (Box 119, Folder 52)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Excel Garment Manufacturing Co., 1961-1966 (Box 119, Folder 53)
- New York Joint Board and F & F Clothiers of New York, Ltd., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 54)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and F & M Clothes, 1960-1968 (Box 119, Folder 55)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Boston Joint Board and Fajoli, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 119, Folder 56)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Family Laundry Owners Association, Inc., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 57)
- New York Joint Board and Famous Coat Front Pad Co., Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- New England, Local #382 and Fashion Line, Inc. (Art Garment Co.), 1956-1970 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts, Local #559 and Fenway Manufacturing Co., 1955-1966 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Local #1714 and Ferro Gloves, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union, Local #1712 and Feuer Hide and Skins Corp., 1972 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Fine Sportswear, 1958-1962 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Harry E. Fiorentino, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union, Local #1712 and Fleming Joffe, Ltd., 1965-1971 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- General Office and Florida Beachwear, Inc., 1959 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Forest City Products, Inc., 1972-1981 (Box 120, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Formal Wear Manufacturing Corp., 1977 (Box 120, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Forte Neckwear Co., Inc., 1962-1968 (Box 120, Folder 12)
- Central States Joint Board and Forty Minute Cleaners, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Irvin B. Foster Sportswear Co., 1958-1972 (Box 120, Folder 14)
- General Office and Fran-Lee Sportswear, Inc., 1956-1961 (Box 120, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Freeland Shirt Co., Inc., 1947-1976 (Box 120, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Frejan Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 120, Folder 17)
- Southern Organizational Department and G.G. Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1965-1976 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  Halls, TN
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and GMTB Laundry Proc., Inc., 1975 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries G & S Linen Service, 1975 (Box 120, Folder 20)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board and Galena Glove and Mitten Co., 1972-1977 (Box 120, Folder 21)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Game & Lake Manufacturing Co., 1961-1962 (Box 120, Folder 22)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Local #1714 and Harry Garfinkle, 1961-1963 (Box 120, Folder 23)
- Cleveland Joint Board and General Athletic Products Co., Inc., 1966-1978 (Box 120, Folder 24)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and General Laundry, 1975 (Box 120, Folder 25)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and General Linen Supply & Laundry Co., Inc., 1975 (Box 120, Folder 26)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Gentry Clothing Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 120, Folder 27)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Paul Gill & Sons, Inc., 1979 (Box 120, Folder 28)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Gina Sportswear, Inc., 1977 (Box 120, Folder 29)
- New York Joint Board and Gino Clothes Sales, Ltd., 1977-1980 (Box 120, Folder 30)
- Rochester Joint Board, Food Workers Local #202-A and Gioia Macaroni Co., Inc., 1961-1981 (Box 120, Folder 31)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Glen Sportswear, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 32)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Glenridge Trouser Corp., 1966-1976 (Box 120, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board and Globe Clothing Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 120, Folder 34)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Globe Pants Manufacturing Co., 1958-1965 (Box 120, Folder 35)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Gloria Sportswear Corp., 1975-1976 (Box 120, Folder 36)
- Massachusetts, Local #689 and Gloucester Pants Co., Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 120, Folder 37)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Glove Button Co., 1966-1970 (Box 120, Folder 38)
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union, Local #1712 and Gloversville Leather, Inc., 1972 (Box 120, Folder 39)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Sigman Goldman, Inc., 1977 (Box 120, Folder 40)
- New York Joint Board and Wm P. Goldman Bros., Inc., 1977 (Box 120, Folder 41)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Stanley H. Goldsmith, Inc., 1977 (Box 120, Folder 42)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Gordon Clothes, Inc., 1971-1979 (Box 120, Folder 43)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Granby Manufacturing Co., 1962-1988 (Box 120, Folder 44)
- Rochester Joint Board and Great Lakes Press Corp., 1973-1976 (Box 120, Folder 45)
- Southern California Joint Board and Grunwald-Marx, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 46)
- Southern Organizational Department and Gulf Apparel Corp., 1980-1983 (Box 120, Folder 47)
- Chicago Joint Board and H.I. Garment Co., 1969 (Box 120, Folder 48)
- New York Joint Board and Halpern & Christenfeld, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 120, Folder 49)
- Southern California Joint Board and Handelsman, 1977-1987 (Box 120, Folder 50)
- Boston Joint Board and Hanover Co., Inc., 1965-1977 (Box 120, Folder 51)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Harbro Manufacturing Corp., 1965-1976 (Box 120, Folder 52)
- Southern California Joint Board and Hartog of California, 1962-1972 (Box 120, Folder 53)
- General Office and Harwood Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 120, Folder 54)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Local #1714 and E.L. Heacock Co., 1961-1963 (Box 120, Folder 55)
- New York Joint Board and Hershey Apparel, Inc., 1977 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Hewell Laundry, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Hewlett Hand Laundry, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and Highlander Sportswear, Inc., 1972-1979 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- General Office and Hiland, Ltd., Inc., 1964-1972 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  Miami, FL
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Hill Top - North Shore Cleaners & Laundry, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Joint Board and Charles Hershey Clothing Co., 1960-1965 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Hobo Apparel, Inc., 1976 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Cincinnati Joint Board and Hochscheid Tailoring Co., 1943-1978 (Box 121, Folder 9)
- Northern California Joint Board, Local #42 and Hodkins Glove Co., 1953-1972 (Box 121, Folder 10)
- Boston Joint Board and M. Hoffman & Co., Inc. (Royal Coat Co., Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 121, Folder 11)
- Southern California Joint Board and Hollywood Clothes, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Homecraft Cleaners Corp., 1975 (Box 121, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Homeway Laundry, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 14)
- Cleaners and Dyers Union, Local #239 and Hooker Chemical Corp. (RC Division), 1966-1969 (Box 121, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board and Yorkshire Neckwear, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 121, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Hy-Richter, Inc., 1977 (Box 121, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Ibla Pants Co., Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 121, Folder 18)
- Maine, Local #667 and Inlet Manufacturing Co., 1953-1969 (Box 121, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and International Hand Laundry, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 20)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Herman Iskin & Company, Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 121, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Island Cascade Linen Supply Co., Inc., 1975 (Box 121, Folder 22)
- General Office and J.H. Manufacturing Co., 1964-1965 (Box 121, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and J & J Hand Laundry Corp., 1975 (Box 121, Folder 24)
- General Office and J & J Silk Screen Printing, 1983 (Box 121, Folder 25)
- Connecticut, Local #125 and J & R Shirt Co., Inc., 1951-1962 (Box 121, Folder 26)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Jackson Heights Laundry & Cleaning Corp., 1975 (Box 121, Folder 27)
- General Office and F. Jacobson & Sons, Inc., 1919-1954 (Box 121, Folder 28)
- Kentuckiana Joint Board, Pennsylvania Joint Board, General Office and F. Jacobson & Sons, Inc., 1955-1972 (Box 121, Folder 29)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Jals Corp., 1961-1962 (Box 121, Folder 30)
- Rochester Joint Board and Walter J. Jamieson Corp., 1969-1975 (Box 121, Folder 31)
- Chicago Joint Board and Arthur Jay Co., 1972 (Box 121, Folder 32)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Jeanette Glove Co., Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 121, Folder 33)
- Virginia, Local #508 and Jefferson Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1960-1971 (Box 121, Folder 34)
- Southern California Joint Board and Alan John Manufacturing Co., 1982 (Box 121, Folder 35)
- Boston Joint Board and Julius & Sons, Inc., 1954-1982 (Box 121, Folder 36)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Kok Corporation, 1972-1975 (Box 121, Folder 37)
- Chicago Joint Board and Kanefield Co., Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 121, Folder 38)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Kansas City Custom Garment Co., 1981 (Box 121, Folder 39)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and S. Kantor Co., 1982 (Box 121, Folder 40)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Kay Bee Sportswear, Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 121, Folder 41)
- Connecticut, Local #125 and Kaybro Corp.(United Shirt & Blouse Co., Inc.), 1958-1961 (Box 121, Folder 42)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Kay's Cleaners & Launderers, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 43)
- New York Joint Board and Max Kirmayer & Sons, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 44)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Kleen Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 121, Folder 45)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Kleen Linen Service, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 46)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Koko Rainwear, 1977-1980 (Box 121, Folder 47)
- Cincinnati Joint Board and Abe Korelitz, 1960 (Box 121, Folder 48)
- California Joint Board and Frank Kucsak Men's Wear & Tailoring, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 49)
- Southern California Joint Board and L & M Manufacturing Co., 1962-1972 (Box 121, Folder 50)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and L & S Sportswear, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 121, Folder 51)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and La Glo Manufacturing Co., 1953-1965 (Box 121, Folder 52)
- California Joint Board and La Jolla Sportswear, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 53)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and La Salle Neckwear Co., 1958-1973 (Box 121, Folder 54)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Lafayette Laundry, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Justin M. Lamm Glove Corp., 1966-1969 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Lanolav Gloves, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and A. LaPolla Uniform Co., 1975-1982 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Chicago Joint Board and Lasalle Quilting Co., 1970 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Lasky Tailors, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Lavendar Cleaning Corp., 1975 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- General Office and Herman K. Lavin Co., 1961 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Lawrence Clothes, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Massachusetts, Local #187 and Lawrence Clothing Manufacturing Co., 1956-1982 (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles Joint Board and Le Nore Garments, Inc., 1958 (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Southern California Joint Board and Leadtec California, Inc., 1975 (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Central States Joint Board and Leather Nu Cleaners, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 13)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board and Ann Lee Sportswear, Inc., 1976 (Box 122, Folder 14)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Sandy Lee Manufacturing Co., 1961-1986 (Box 122, Folder 15)
- New York Joint Board and Leifner Uniform Co., 1975-1982 (Box 122, Folder 16)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Les Brown Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 122, Folder 17)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear and Levinsohn Designs, Ltd., 1975 (Box 122, Folder 18)
- Southern Organizational Department and Lewisburg Sportswear, Inc., 1967-1974 (Box 122, Folder 19)
- New York Joint Board and Lexington National Tailoring Co., 1975-1982 (Box 122, Folder 20)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Libas, Ltd., 1983 (Box 122, Folder 21)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Liberty Garment Manufacturing Co., 1965-1968 (Box 122, Folder 22)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Liberty Sport Togs, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 122, Folder 23)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Liberty Tailoring Co., 1960-1963 (Box 122, Folder 24)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Chas H. Liebman & Bros., Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 122, Folder 25)
- Southern California Joint Board and Linda of California, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 26)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Linens of the Week, Inc., 1975 (Box 122, Folder 27)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Linn Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969 (Box 122, Folder 28)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Little Ego, Ltd., 1973 (Box 122, Folder 29)
- North Alabama Area Joint Board and Livingston Manufacturing Co., 1981-1983 (Box 122, Folder 30)
- Chicago Joint Board and Tony Llad Leather, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 31)
- Southern California Joint Board and Los Angeles Sportogs, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 122, Folder 32)
- Local #694 and Lov's Tailoring & Uniform Co., Inc., 1964 (Box 122, Folder 33)
- General Office and Louisville Garment Co. (Mississippi), 1966-1972 (Box 122, Folder 34)
- General Office and Louisville Pants Corp., 1956-1976 (Box 122, Folder 35)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Loysone Glove Co., 1965 (Box 122, Folder 36)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Lustberg, Nast & Co., Inc., 1941-1958 (Box 122, Folder 37)
- Massachusetts, Local #187 and Lyn-Del Corp., 1951-1972 (Box 122, Folder 38)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Madison Red Star Linen Laundries, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 39)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and S. Maiocco Tailoring, 1977-1982 (Box 122, Folder 40)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Major Lane Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 122, Folder 41)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Herman Mandel, 1960-1963 (Box 122, Folder 42)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Morris Mandel, 1960-1972 (Box 122, Folder 43)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Manhattan Sponging Works, Inc., 1964-1973 (Box 122, Folder 44)
- New York Joint Board and S. Manzo's Tailoring Co., 1977-1982 (Box 122, Folder 45)
- Tannery and Leather Workers' Union, Local #1712 and Maranco Leather, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 122, Folder 46)
- New York Joint Board and Mancan Clothes, 1977-1982 (Box 122, Folder 47)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Marguerite Glove Co., 1964-1967 (Box 122, Folder 48)
- New York Joint Board and Marsy Clothes, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 122, Folder 49)
- Southern Organizational Department and Mal Marshall, Inc., 1957-1980 (Box 122, Folder 50)
- Capitol District Joint Board and Marshall Ray Corp., 1957-1976 (Box 122, Folder 51)
- Massachusetts, Local #377 and Massachusetts Shirt Manufacturing Corp., 1966 (Box 122, Folder 52)
- General Office and Master Slack Corp. (Bolivar, TN), 1981 (Box 122, Folder 53)
- Southern California Joint Board and Maurice Slacks, 1974-1976 (Box 122, Folder 54)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Maury Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 122, Folder 55)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Mavest, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 122, Folder 56)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #353 and Mayflower Coat Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1962-1979 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and McGrath Coat Co., Inc., 1966-1972 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Toronto Joint Board and James B. McGregor, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Southern Organizational Department and Mewdow Sportswear Co., 1972 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Medical Arts Linen Service Corp., 1975 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Mediterranean Tailors, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Medvinsky Salvage, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Mellish Farms, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- Chicago Joint Board and Menser Industries, Inc., 1968-1976 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Mercury Uniform Rental Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Metcalf Neckwear Co., 1970 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board and Meyers N.C., Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- General Office and Miami Pants, 1959-1961 (Box 123, Folder 13)
- Chicago Joint Board and Amy Michelle Co., Inc., 1972 (Box 123, Folder 14)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Mid-American Textiles, Inc., 1977 (Box 123, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board and Mid Town Bank of Chicago, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 16)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Daniel C. Miller Glove Co., 1967-1974 (Box 123, Folder 17)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Fred C. Miller Glove Co., 1967-1972 (Box 123, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Jack Miller Coat Front Co., 1963-1971 (Box 123, Folder 19)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Milwaukee Joint Board and Milwaukee Dye & Bleaching Co., 1968-1985 (Box 123, Folder 20)